{
    "Q1": {
        "levels": {
            "1": [
                {
                    "question": "3 + 4?",
                    "answer": "7",
                    "hint": "7"
                },
                {
                    "question": "7 + 7?",
                    "answer": "14",
                    "hint": "14"
                },
                {
                    "question": "6 + 5?",
                    "answer": "11",
                    "hint": "11"
                },
                {
                    "question": "12 + 8?",
                    "answer": "20",
                    "hint": "20"
                }
            ],
            "2": [
                {
                    "question": "15 - 5?",
                    "answer": "10",
                    "hint": "10"
                },
                {
                    "question": "23 - 8?",
                    "answer": "15",
                    "hint": "15"
                },
                {
                    "question": "40 - 30?",
                    "answer": "10",
                    "hint": "10"
                },
                {
                    "question": "42 - 19?",
                    "answer": "23",
                    "hint": "23"
                }
            ],
            "3": [
                {
                    "question": "6 * 6?",
                    "answer": "36",
                    "hint": "36"
                },
                {
                    "question": "4 * 6?",
                    "answer": "24",
                    "hint": "24"
                },
                {
                    "question": "2 * 9?",
                    "answer": "18",
                    "hint": "18"
                },
                {
                    "question": "9 * 8?",
                    "answer": "72",
                    "hint": "72"
                }
            ],
            "4": [
                {
                    "question": "55 / 11?",
                    "answer": "5",
                    "hint": "5"
                },
                {
                    "question": "12 / 4?",
                    "answer": "3",
                    "hint": "3"
                },
                {
                    "question": "42 / 7?",
                    "answer": "6",
                    "hint": "6"
                },
                {
                    "question": "22 / 2?",
                    "answer": "11",
                    "hint": "11"
                }
            ],
            "Test": [
                {
                    "question": "4 * 6?",
                    "answer": "24",
                    "hint": "24"
                },
                {
                    "question": "42 / 7?",
                    "answer": "6",
                    "hint": "6"
                },
                {
                    "question": "2 * 9?",
                    "answer": "18",
                    "hint": "18"
                },
                {
                    "question": "40 - 30?",
                    "answer": "10",
                    "hint": "10"
                },
                {
                    "question": "12 / 4?",
                    "answer": "3",
                    "hint": "3"
                },
                {
                    "question": "7 + 7?",
                    "answer": "14",
                    "hint": "14"
                },
                {
                    "question": "42 - 19?",
                    "answer": "23",
                    "hint": "23"
                },
                {
                    "question": "15 - 5?",
                    "answer": "10",
                    "hint": "10"
                },
                {
                    "question": "6 + 5?",
                    "answer": "11",
                    "hint": "11"
                },
                {
                    "question": "3 + 4?",
                    "answer": "7",
                    "hint": "7"
                }
            ]
        }
    },
    "Q2": {
        "levels": {
            "1": [
                {
                    "question": "5 + 3?",
                    "answer": "8",
                    "hint": "8"
                },
                {
                    "question": "8 + 6?",
                    "answer": "14",
                    "hint": "14"
                },
                {
                    "question": "9 + 4?",
                    "answer": "13",
                    "hint": "13"
                },
                {
                    "question": "11 + 9?",
                    "answer": "20",
                    "hint": "20"
                }
            ],
            "2": [
                {
                    "question": "18 - 9?",
                    "answer": "9",
                    "hint": "9"
                },
                {
                    "question": "25 - 10?",
                    "answer": "15",
                    "hint": "15"
                },
                {
                    "question": "50 - 35?",
                    "answer": "15",
                    "hint": "15"
                },
                {
                    "question": "37 - 14?",
                    "answer": "23",
                    "hint": "23"
                }
            ],
            "3": [
                {
                    "question": "5 * 5?",
                    "answer": "25",
                    "hint": "25"
                },
                {
                    "question": "7 * 4?",
                    "answer": "28",
                    "hint": "28"
                },
                {
                    "question": "3 * 7?",
                    "answer": "21",
                    "hint": "21"
                },
                {
                    "question": "8 * 6?",
                    "answer": "48",
                    "hint": "48"
                }
            ],
            "4": [
                {
                    "question": "49 / 7?",
                    "answer": "7",
                    "hint": "7"
                },
                {
                    "question": "24 / 8?",
                    "answer": "3",
                    "hint": "3"
                },
                {
                    "question": "63 / 9?",
                    "answer": "7",
                    "hint": "7"
                },
                {
                    "question": "36 / 6?",
                    "answer": "6",
                    "hint": "6"
                }
            ],
            "Test": [
                {
                    "question": "8 * 6?",
                    "answer": "48",
                    "hint": "48"
                },
                {
                    "question": "36 / 6?",
                    "answer": "6",
                    "hint": "6"
                },
                {
                    "question": "3 * 7?",
                    "answer": "21",
                    "hint": "21"
                },
                {
                    "question": "50 - 35?",
                    "answer": "15",
                    "hint": "15"
                },
                {
                    "question": "24 / 8?",
                    "answer": "3",
                    "hint": "3"
                },
                {
                    "question": "8 + 6?",
                    "answer": "14",
                    "hint": "14"
                },
                {
                    "question": "37 - 14?",
                    "answer": "23",
                    "hint": "23"
                },
                {
                    "question": "18 - 9?",
                    "answer": "9",
                    "hint": "9"
                },
                {
                    "question": "9 + 4?",
                    "answer": "13",
                    "hint": "13"
                },
                {
                    "question": "5 + 3?",
                    "answer": "8",
                    "hint": "8"
                }
            ]
        }
    },
    "Q3": {
        "levels": {
            "1": [
                {
                    "question": "What is 8 + 2?",
                    "answer": "10",
                    "hint": "How many fingers do you have?"
                }
            ]
        }
    }
}